<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="billres.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE resolution PUBLIC "-//US Congress//DTDs/res.dtd//EN" "res.dtd">
<resolution public-private="public" resolution-stage="Agreed-to-Senate" resolution-type="senate-resolution" star-print="no-star-print">

	<form display="yes">

		<distribution-code display="yes">III </distribution-code>

		<congress display="yes">109th CONGRESS</congress>

		<session display="yes">1st Session</session>

		<legis-num>S. RES. 6</legis-num>

		<current-chamber>IN THE SENATE OF THE UNITED STATES</current-chamber>

		<action display="yes">

			<action-date date="20050106">January 6, 2005</action-date>

			<action-desc blank-lines-after="0" display="yes">

				<sponsor by-request="no" name-id="S198">Mr. Reid</sponsor> submitted the

			 following resolution; which was considered and agreed to</action-desc>

		</action>

		<legis-type>RESOLUTION</legis-type>

		<official-title display="yes">Making minority party appointments to

		  certain Senate committees for the 109th Congress.</official-title>

	</form>

	<resolution-body display-resolving-clause="yes-display-resolving-clause" style="OLC">

		<section commented="no" display-inline="yes-display-inline" id="S1" section-type="undesignated-section">

			<text display-inline="yes-display-inline">That notwithstanding the

			 provisions of Rule XXV, the following shall constitute the minority party's

			 membership on the following standing committees for the One Hundred Ninth

			 Congress, or until their successors are chosen:</text>

			<subsection id="id9577F7E457F747EC8AF26F8E77B80930"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry</header-in-text>: Mr. Harkin (Ranking

			 Member), Mr. Leahy, Mr. Conrad, Mr. Baucus, Mrs. Lincoln, Ms. Stabenow, Mr.

			 Nelson of Nebraska, Mr. Dayton, and Mr. Salazar.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idF460885D700D453CB345AE822B785439"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Appropriations</header-in-text>: Mr. Byrd (Ranking Member), Mr. Inouye, Mr.

			 Leahy, Mr. Harkin, Ms. Mikulski, Mr. Reid, Mr. Kohl, Mrs. Murray, Mr. Dorgan,

			 Mrs. Feinstein, Mr. Durbin, Mr. Johnson, and Ms. Landrieu.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idB49AE49F8FAD4C5BAB8F36AA1E72F880"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Armed Services</header-in-text>: Mr. Levin (Ranking Member), Mr. Kennedy, Mr.

			 Byrd, Mr. Lieberman, Mr. Reed, Mr. Akaka, Mr. Nelson of Florida, Mr. Nelson of

			 Nebraska, Mr. Dayton, Mr. Bayh, and Mrs. Clinton.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id099D784DC068400E88DE34C53F647D1B"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs</header-in-text>: Mr. Sarbanes (Ranking

			 Member), Mr. Dodd, Mr. Johnson, Mr. Reed, Mr. Schumer, Mr. Bayh, Mr. Carper,

			 Ms. Stabenow, and Mr. Corzine.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idA65E1DD8F5C14CFBBC8C1077A16573A3"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Commerce, Science, and Transportation</header-in-text>: Mr. Inouye (Ranking

			 Member), Mr. Rockefeller, Mr. Kerry, Mr. Dorgan, Mrs. Boxer, Mr. Nelson of

			 Florida, Ms. Cantwell, Mr. Lautenberg, Mr. Nelson of Nebraska, and Mr.

			 Pryor.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id6067B6C1B7DB476A90A441B7DC79DF35"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Energy and Natural Resources</header-in-text>: Mr. Bingaman (Ranking Member),

			 Mr. Akaka, Mr. Dorgan, Mr. Wyden, Mr. Johnson, Ms. Landrieu, Mrs. Feinstein,

			 Ms. Cantwell, Mr. Corzine, and Mr. Salazar.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id5F96F64E3CD044149F41181308427BF7"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Environment and Public Works</header-in-text>: Mr. Jeffords (Ranking Member),

			 Mr. Baucus, Mr. Lieberman, Mrs. Boxer, Mr. Carper, Mrs. Clinton, Mr.

			 Lautenberg, and Mr. Obama.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id3B21E6E65AC144F19666C9056CB2CB47"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Finance</header-in-text>: Mr. Baucus (Ranking Member), Mr. Rockefeller, Mr.

			 Conrad, Mr. Jeffords, Mr. Bingaman, Mr. Kerry, Mrs. Lincoln, Mr. Wyden, and Mr.

			 Schumer.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id3056D5701BFB4C9DABFF50D6AEA601CF"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Foreign Relations</header-in-text>: Mr. Biden (Ranking Member), Mr. Sarbanes,

			 Mr. Dodd, Mr. Kerry, Mr. Feingold, Mrs. Boxer, Mr. Nelson of Florida, and Mr.

			 Obama.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idC7D37135AB1D4EA690FCD83B25148E4F"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Health, Education, Labor, and Pensions</header-in-text>: Mr. Kennedy (Ranking

			 Member), Mr. Dodd, Mr. Harkin, Ms. Mikulski, Mr. Jeffords, Mr. Bingaman, Mrs.

			 Murray, Mr. Reed, and Mrs. Clinton.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idA2464AFA71734C088AF1878919FCB915"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Homeland Security and Governmental Affairs</header-in-text>: Mr. Lieberman

			 (Ranking Member), Mr. Levin, Mr. Akaka, Mr. Carper, Mr. Dayton, Mr. Lautenberg,

			 and Mr. Pryor.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id2D306E755C9E4653A2464ABB984722B7"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on the

			 Judiciary</header-in-text>: Mr. Leahy (Ranking Member), Mr. Kennedy, Mr. Biden,

			 Mr. Kohl, Mrs. Feinstein, Mr. Feingold, Mr. Schumer, and Mr. Durbin.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id912A5488B07142CFB79F432E0073DABB"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Rules and Administration</header-in-text>: Mr. Dodd (Ranking Member), Mr. Byrd,

			 Mr. Inouye, Mrs. Feinstein, Mr. Schumer, Mr. Dayton, Mr. Durbin, and Mr. Nelson

			 of Nebraska.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idE9315A3449844142B3F6323D101538E3"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Small Business and Entrepreneurship</header-in-text>: Mr. Kerry (Ranking

			 Member), Mr. Levin, Mr. Harkin, Mr. Lieberman, Ms. Landrieu, Ms. Cantwell, Mr.

			 Bayh, and Mr. Pryor.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id705013D945DC454DAC89FF0085346A75"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Veterans' Affairs</header-in-text>: Mr. Akaka (Ranking Member), Mr.

			 Rockefeller, Mr. Jeffords, Mrs. Murray, Mr. Obama, and Mr. Salazar.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id6B8BAFB0FB86431BA93974DA5F8F24E3"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Special Committee

			 on Aging</header-in-text>: Mr. Kohl (Ranking Member), Mr. Jeffords, Mr.

			 Feingold, Mr. Wyden, Mrs. Lincoln, Mr. Bayh, Mr. Carper, Mr. Nelson of Florida,

			 and Mrs. Clinton.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id33711FB97679414298D129972DBC41B2"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on the

			 Budget</header-in-text>: Mr. Conrad (Ranking Member), Mr. Sarbanes, Mrs.

			 Murray, Mr. Wyden, Mr. Feingold, Mr. Johnson, Mr. Byrd, Mr. Nelson of Florida,

			 Ms. Stabenow, and Mr. Corzine.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id0E0514AD77E84020AC19664BAFB23AD2"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Select Committee

			 on Ethics</header-in-text>: Mr. Johnson (Vice Chairman), Mr. Akaka, and Mr.

			 Pryor.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idADE8E3C66AED43FEA5E22057529DE13C"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Indian Affairs</header-in-text>: Mr. Dorgan (Vice Chairman), Mr. Inouye, Mr.

			 Conrad, Mr. Akaka, Mr. Johnson, and Ms. Cantwell.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idBFC81DC7B0BA46B7B7151FB59E74B424"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Select Committee

			 on Intelligence</header-in-text>: Mr. Rockefeller (Vice Chairman), Mr. Levin,

			 Mrs. Feinstein, Mr. Wyden, Mr. Bayh, Ms. Mikulski, and Mr. Corzine.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id6081A10533544DC79D6AC4508EF9456A"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Joint Economic

			 Committee</header-in-text>: Mr. Reed, Mr. Kennedy, Mr. Sarbanes, and Mr.

			 Bingaman.</text>

			</subsection></section></resolution-body>

</resolution>

