<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="billres.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE resolution PUBLIC "-//US Congress//DTDs/res.dtd//EN" "res.dtd">
<resolution public-private="public" resolution-stage="Agreed-to-Senate" resolution-type="senate-resolution" star-print="no-star-print">

	<form display="yes">

		<distribution-code display="yes">III </distribution-code>

		<congress display="yes">109th CONGRESS</congress>

		<session display="yes">1st Session</session>

		<legis-num>S. RES. 5</legis-num>

		<current-chamber>IN THE SENATE OF THE UNITED STATES</current-chamber>

		<action display="yes">

			<action-date date="20050106">January 6, 2005</action-date>

			<action-desc blank-lines-after="0" display="yes">

				<sponsor by-request="no" name-id="S241">Mr. Frist</sponsor> submitted the

			 following resolution; which was considered and agreed to</action-desc>

		</action>

		<legis-type>RESOLUTION</legis-type>

		<official-title display="yes">Making majority party appointments to

		  certain Senate committees for the 109th Congress.</official-title>

	</form>

	<resolution-body display-resolving-clause="yes-display-resolving-clause" style="OLC">

		<section commented="no" display-inline="yes-display-inline" id="S1" section-type="undesignated-section">

			<text display-inline="yes-display-inline">That notwithstanding the

			 provisions of Rule XXV, the following shall constitute the majority party's

			 membership on the following standing committees for the One Hundred Ninth

			 Congress, or until their successors are chosen:</text>

			<subsection id="id9577F7E457F747EC8AF26F8E77B80930"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry</header-in-text>: Mr. Chambliss

			 (Chairman), Mr. Lugar, Mr. Cochran, Mr. McConnell, Mr. Roberts, Mr. Talent, Mr.

			 Thomas, Mr. Santorum, Mr. Coleman, Mr. Crapo, and Mr. Grassley.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idF460885D700D453CB345AE822B785439"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Appropriations</header-in-text>: Mr. Cochran (Chairman), Mr. Stevens, Mr.

			 Specter, Mr. Domenici, Mr. Bond, Mr. McConnell, Mr. Burns, Mr. Shelby, Mr.

			 Gregg, Mr. Bennett, Mr. Craig, Mrs. Hutchison, Mr. DeWine, Mr. Brownback, and

			 Mr. Allard.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idB49AE49F8FAD4C5BAB8F36AA1E72F880"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Armed Services</header-in-text>: Mr. Warner (Chairman), Mr. McCain, Mr. Inhofe,

			 Mr. Roberts, Mr. Sessions, Ms. Collins, Mr. Ensign, Mr. Talent, Mr. Chambliss,

			 Mr. Graham, Mrs. Dole, Mr. Cornyn, and Mr. Thune.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id099D784DC068400E88DE34C53F647D1B"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs</header-in-text>: Mr. Shelby (Chairman),

			 Mr. Bennett, Mr. Allard, Mr. Enzi, Mr. Hagel, Mr. Santorum, Mr. Bunning, Mr.

			 Crapo, Mr. Sununu, Mrs. Dole, and Mr. Martinez.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idA65E1DD8F5C14CFBBC8C1077A16573A3"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Commerce, Science, and Transportation</header-in-text>: Mr. Stevens (Chairman),

			 Mr. McCain, Mr. Burns, Mr. Lott, Mrs. Hutchison, Ms. Snowe, Mr. Smith, Mr.

			 Ensign, Mr. Allen, Mr. Sununu, Mr. Demint, and Mr. Vitter.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id6067B6C1B7DB476A90A441B7DC79DF35"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Energy and Natural Resources</header-in-text>: Mr. Domenici (Chairman), Mr.

			 Craig, Mr. Thomas, Mr. Alexander, Ms. Murkowski, Mr. Burr, Mr. Martinez, Mr.

			 Talent, Mr. Burns, Mr. Allen, Mr. Smith, and Mr. Bunning.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id5F96F64E3CD044149F41181308427BF7"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Environment and Public Works</header-in-text>: Mr. Inhofe (Chairman), Mr.

			 Warner, Mr. Bond, Mr. Voinovich, Mr. Chafee, Ms. Murkowski, Mr. Thune, Mr.

			 Demint, Mr. Isakson, and Mr. Vitter.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id3B21E6E65AC144F19666C9056CB2CB47"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Finance</header-in-text>: Mr. Grassley (Chairman), Mr. Hatch, Mr. Lott, Ms.

			 Snowe, Mr. Kyl, Mr. Thomas, Mr. Santorum, Mr. Frist, Mr. Smith, Mr. Bunning,

			 and Mr. Crapo.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id3056D5701BFB4C9DABFF50D6AEA601CF"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Foreign Relations</header-in-text>: Mr. Lugar (Chairman), Mr. Hagel, Mr.

			 Chafee, Mr. Allen, Mr. Coleman, Mr. Voinovich, Mr. Alexander, Mr. Sununu, Ms.

			 Murkowski, and Mr. Martinez.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idC7D37135AB1D4EA690FCD83B25148E4F"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Health, Education, Labor, and Pensions</header-in-text>: Mr. Enzi (Chairman),

			 Mr. Gregg, Mr. Frist, Mr. Alexander, Mr. Burr, Mr. Isakson, Mr. DeWine, Mr.

			 Ensign, Mr. Hatch, Mr. Sessions, and Mr. Roberts.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idA2464AFA71734C088AF1878919FCB915"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Homeland Security and Govermental Affairs</header-in-text>: Ms. Collins

			 (Chairman), Mr. Stevens, Mr. Voinovich, Mr. Coleman, Mr. Coburn, Mr. Chafee,

			 Mr. Bennett, Mr. Domenici, and Mr. Warner.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id2D306E755C9E4653A2464ABB984722B7"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Select Committee

			 on Intelligence</header-in-text>: Mr. Roberts (Chairman), Mr. Hatch, Mr.

			 DeWine, Mr. Bond, Mr. Lott, Ms. Snowe, Mr. Hagel, Mr. Chambliss, and Mr. Warner

			 (ex officio).</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id0C3AEA2638644CC8931EC01BB11EC04C"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on the

			 Judiciary</header-in-text>: Mr. Specter (Chairman), Mr. Hatch, Mr. Grassley,

			 Mr. Kyl, Mr. DeWine, Mr. Sessions, Mr. Graham, Mr. Cornyn, Mr. Brownback, and

			 Mr. Coburn.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id705013D945DC454DAC89FF0085346A75"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Special Committee

			 on Aging</header-in-text>: Mr. Smith (Chairman), Mr. Shelby, Ms. Collins, Mr.

			 Talent, Mrs. Dole, Mr. Martinez, Mr. Craig, Mr. Santorum, Mr. Burns, Mr.

			 Alexander, and Mr. Demint.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id33711FB97679414298D129972DBC41B2"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on the

			 Budget</header-in-text>: Mr. Gregg (Chairman), Mr. Domenici, Mr. Grassley, Mr.

			 Allard, Mr. Enzi, Mr. Sessions, Mr. Bunning, Mr. Crapo, Mr. Ensign, Mr. Cornyn,

			 Mr. Alexander, and Mr. Graham.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id0E0514AD77E84020AC19664BAFB23AD2"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Select Committee

			 on Ethics</header-in-text>: Mr. Voinovich (Chairman), Mr. Roberts, and Mr.

			 Thomas.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idADE8E3C66AED43FEA5E22057529DE13C"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Indian Affairs</header-in-text>: Mr. McCain (Chairman), Mr. Thomas, Ms.

			 Murkowski, Mr. Coburn, Mr. Domenici, Mr. Smith, Mr. Crapo, and Mr. Burr.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id6081A10533544DC79D6AC4508EF9456A"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Joint Economic

			 Committee</header-in-text>: Mr. Bennett (Vice-Chairman), Mr. Brownback, Mr.

			 Sununu, Mr. Demint, Mr. Sessions, and Mr. Cornyn.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="id912A5488B07142CFB79F432E0073DABB"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Rules and Administration</header-in-text>: Mr. Lott (Chairman), Mr. Stevens,

			 Mr. McConnell, Mr. Cochran, Mr. Santorum, Mr. Frist, Mr. Chambliss, Mrs.

			 Hutchison, Mr. Bennett, and Mr. Hagel.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idE9315A3449844142B3F6323D101538E3"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Small Business and Entrepreneurship</header-in-text>: Ms. Snowe (Chairman), Mr.

			 Bond, Mr. Burns, Mr. Allen, Mr. Coleman, Mr. Thune, Mr. Isakson, Mr. Vitter,

			 Mr. Enzi, and Mr. Cornyn.</text>

			</subsection><subsection id="idFB023989034D4D24BF3F14F88F57CA6D"><enum></enum><text><header-in-text>Committee on

			 Veterans' Affairs</header-in-text>: Mr. Craig (Chairman), Mr. Specter, Mrs.

			 Hutchison, Mr. Graham, Mr. Burr, Mr. Ensign, Mr. Thune, and Mr. Isakson.</text>

			</subsection></section></resolution-body>

</resolution>

