<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="billres.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE resolution PUBLIC "-//US Congress//DTDs/res.dtd//EN" "res.dtd">
<resolution public-private="public" resolution-stage="Agreed-to-Senate" resolution-type="senate-resolution">
	<form>
		<distribution-code display="yes">III</distribution-code>
		<congress>111th CONGRESS</congress>
		<session>2d Session</session>
		<legis-num>S. RES. 594</legis-num>
		<current-chamber>IN THE SENATE OF THE UNITED STATES</current-chamber>
		<action>
			<action-date date="20100721">July 22, 2010</action-date>
			<action-desc><sponsor name-id="S198">Mr. Reid</sponsor> submitted the
			 following resolution; which was considered and agreed to</action-desc>
		</action>
		<legis-type>RESOLUTION</legis-type>
		<official-title display="yes">To constitute the majority party's
		  membership on certain committees for the One Hundred Eleventh Congress, or
		  until their successors are chosen.</official-title>
	</form>
	<resolution-body>
		<section display-inline="yes-display-inline" id="S1" section-type="undesignated-section"><enum></enum><text>That the following shall constitute
			 the majority party's membership on the following committees for the One Hundred
			 Eleventh Congress, or until their successors are chosen:</text>
			<committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on
			 appropriations:</header><text>Mr. Inouye (Chairman), Mr. Leahy, Mr. Harkin, Ms.
			 Mikulski, Mr. Kohl, Mrs. Murray, Mr. Dorgan, Mrs. Feinstein, Mr. Durbin, Mr.
			 Johnson, Ms. Landrieu, Mr. Reed, Mr. Lautenberg, Mr. Nelson (Nebraska), Mr.
			 Pryor, Mr. Tester, Mr. Specter, and Mr. Brown (Ohio).</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on armed
			 services:</header><text>Mr. Levin (Chairman), Mr. Lieberman, Mr. Reed, Mr.
			 Akaka, Mr. Nelson (Florida), Mr. Nelson (Nebraska), Mr. Bayh, Mr. Webb, Mrs.
			 McCaskill, Mr. Udall (Colorado), Mrs. Hagan, Mr. Begich, Mr. Burris, Mr.
			 Bingaman, Mr. Kaufman, and Mr. Goodwin.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on the
			 budget:</header><text>Mr. Conrad (Chairman), Mrs. Murray, Mr. Wyden, Mr.
			 Feingold, Mr. Nelson (Florida), Ms. Stabenow, Mr. Cardin, Mr. Sanders, Mr.
			 Whitehouse, Mr. Warner, Mr. Merkley, Mr. Begich, and Mr. Goodwin.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on health, education,
			 labor, and pensions:</header><text>Mr. Harkin (Chairman), Mr. Dodd, Ms.
			 Mikulski, Mr. Bingaman, Mrs. Murray, Mr. Reed, Mr. Sanders, Mr. Casey, Mrs.
			 Hagan, Mr. Merkley, Mr. Franken, Mr. Bennet, and Mr. Goodwin.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on rules and
			 administration:</header><text>Mr. Schumer (Chairman), Mr. Inouye, Mr. Dodd,
			 Mrs. Feinstein, Mr. Durbin, Mr. Nelson (Nebraska), Mrs. Murray, Mr. Pryor, Mr.
			 Udall (New Mexico), Mr. Warner, and Mr. Goodwin.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph></section></resolution-body>
</resolution>
