<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="billres.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE resolution PUBLIC "-//US Congress//DTDs/res.dtd//EN" "res.dtd">
<resolution public-private="public" resolution-stage="Agreed-to-Senate" resolution-type="senate-resolution" star-print="no-star-print">
	<form>
		<distribution-code display="yes">III</distribution-code>
		<congress display="yes">112th CONGRESS</congress>
		<session display="yes">1st Session</session>
		<legis-num>S. RES. 42</legis-num>
		<current-chamber>IN THE SENATE OF THE UNITED STATES</current-chamber>
		<action display="yes">
			<action-date>February 3, 2011</action-date>
			<action-desc><sponsor name-id="S198">Mr. Reid</sponsor> submitted the
			 following resolution; which was considered and agreed to</action-desc>
		</action>
		<legis-type>RESOLUTION</legis-type>
		<official-title display="yes">To constitute the majority party's
		  membership on certain committees for the One Hundred Twelfth Congress, or until
		  their successors are chosen.</official-title>
	</form>
	<resolution-body>
		<section display-inline="yes-display-inline" id="S1" section-type="undesignated-section"><enum></enum><text>That the following shall constitute
			 the majority party's membership on the following committees for the One Hundred
			 Twelfth Congress, or until their successors are chosen:</text>
			<committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Agriculture,
			 Nutrition, and Forestry:</header><text>Ms. Stabenow (Chairman), Mr. Leahy, Mr.
			 Harkin, Mr. Conrad, Mr. Baucus, Mr. Nelson (Nebraska), Mr. Brown (Ohio), Mr.
			 Casey, Ms. Klobuchar, Mr. Bennet, and Mrs. Gillibrand.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on
			 Appropriations:</header><text>Mr. Inouye (Chairman), Mr. Leahy, Mr. Harkin, Ms.
			 Mikulski, Mr. Kohl, Mrs. Murray, Mrs. Feinstein, Mr. Durbin, Mr. Johnson (South
			 Dakota), Ms. Landrieu, Mr. Reed, Mr. Lautenberg, Mr. Nelson (Nebraska), Mr.
			 Pryor, Mr. Tester, and Mr. Brown (Ohio).</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Armed
			 Services:</header><text>Mr. Levin (Chairman), Mr. Lieberman, Mr. Reed, Mr.
			 Akaka, Mr. Nelson (Nebraska), Mr. Webb, Mrs. McCaskill, Mr. Udall (Colorado),
			 Mrs. Hagan, Mr. Begich, Mr. Manchin, Mrs. Shaheen, Mrs. Gillibrand, and Mr.
			 Blumenthal.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Banking, Housing,
			 and Urban Affairs:</header><text>Mr. Johnson (South Dakota) (Chairman), Mr.
			 Reed, Mr. Schumer, Mr. Menendez, Mr. Akaka, Mr. Brown (Ohio), Mr. Tester, Mr.
			 Kohl, Mr. Warner, Mr. Merkley, Mr. Bennet, and Mrs. Hagan.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Commerce, Science,
			 and Transportation:</header><text>Mr. Rockefeller (Chairman), Mr. Inouye, Mr.
			 Kerry, Mrs. Boxer, Mr. Nelson (Florida), Ms. Cantwell, Mr. Lautenberg, Mr.
			 Pryor, Mrs. McCaskill, Ms. Klobuchar, Mr. Udall (New Mexico), Mr. Warner, and
			 Mr. Begich.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Energy and Natural
			 Resources:</header><text>Mr. Bingaman (Chairman), Mr. Wyden, Mr. Johnson (South
			 Dakota), Ms. Landrieu, Ms. Cantwell, Mr. Sanders, Ms. Stabenow, Mr. Udall
			 (Colorado), Mrs. Shaheen, Mr. Franken, Mr. Manchin, and Mr. Coons.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on the Environment and
			 Public Works:</header><text>Mrs. Boxer (Chairman), Mr. Baucus, Mr. Carper, Mr.
			 Lautenberg, Mr. Cardin, Mr. Sanders, Mr. Whitehouse, Mr. Udall (New Mexico),
			 Mr. Merkley, and Mrs. Gillibrand.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on
			 Finance:</header><text>Mr. Baucus (Chairman), Mr. Rockefeller, Mr. Conrad, Mr.
			 Bingaman, Mr. Kerry, Mr. Wyden, Mr. Schumer, Ms. Stabenow, Ms. Cantwell, Mr.
			 Nelson (Florida), Mr. Menendez, Mr. Carper, and Mr. Cardin.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Foreign
			 Relations:</header><text>Mr. Kerry (Chairman), Mrs. Boxer, Mr. Menendez, Mr.
			 Cardin, Mr. Casey, Mr. Webb, Mrs. Shaheen, Mr. Coons, Mr. Durbin, and Mr. Udall
			 (New Mexico).</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Health, Education,
			 Labor, and Pensions:</header><text>Mr. Harkin (Chairman), Ms. Mikulski, Mr.
			 Bingaman, Mrs. Murray, Mr. Sanders, Mr. Casey, Mrs. Hagan, Mr. Merkley, Mr.
			 Franken, Mr. Bennet, Mr. Whitehouse, and Mr. Blumenthal.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Homeland Security
			 and Governmental Affairs:</header><text>Mr. Lieberman (Chairman), Mr. Levin,
			 Mr. Akaka, Mr. Carper, Mr. Pryor, Ms. Landrieu, Mrs. McCaskill, Mr. Tester, and
			 Mr. Begich.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on the
			 Judiciary:</header><text>Mr. Leahy (Chairman), Mr. Kohl, Mrs. Feinstein, Mr.
			 Schumer, Mr. Durbin, Mr. Whitehouse, Ms. Klobuchar, Mr. Franken, Mr. Coons, and
			 Mr. Blumenthal.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Select Committee on
			 Intelligence:</header><text>Mrs. Feinstein (Chairman), Mr. Rockefeller, Mr.
			 Wyden, Ms. Mikulski, Mr. Nelson (Florida), Mr. Conrad, Mr. Udall (Colorado),
			 and Mr. Warner.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on the
			 Budget:</header><text>Mr. Conrad (Chairman), Mrs. Murray, Mr. Wyden, Mr. Nelson
			 (Florida), Ms. Stabenow, Mr. Cardin, Mr. Sanders, Mr. Whitehouse, Mr. Warner,
			 Mr. Merkley, Mr. Begich, and Mr. Coons.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Rules and
			 Administration:</header><text>Mr. Schumer (Chairman), Mr. Inouye, Mrs.
			 Feinstein, Mr. Durbin, Mr. Nelson (Nebraska), Mrs. Murray, Mr. Pryor, Mr. Udall
			 (New Mexico), Mr. Warner, and Mr. Leahy.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Small Business and
			 Entrepreneurship:</header><text>Ms. Landrieu (Chairman), Mr. Levin, Mr. Harkin,
			 Mr. Kerry, Mr. Lieberman, Ms. Cantwell, Mr. Pryor, Mr. Cardin, Mrs. Shaheen,
			 and Mrs. Hagan.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Veterans'
			 Affairs:</header><text>Mrs. Murray (Chairman), Mr. Rockefeller, Mr. Akaka, Mr.
			 Sanders, Mr. Brown (Ohio), Mr. Webb, Mr. Tester, and Mr. Begich.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Special Committee on
			 Aging:</header><text>Mr. Kohl (Chairman), Mr. Wyden, Mr. Nelson (Florida), Mr.
			 Casey, Mrs. McCaskill, Mr. Whitehouse, Mr. Udall (Colorado), Mr. Bennet, Mrs.
			 Gillibrand, Mr. Manchin, and Mr. Blumenthal.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Joint Economic
			 Committee:</header><text>Mr. Casey (Chairman), Mr. Bingaman, Ms. Klobuchar, Mr.
			 Webb, Mr. Warner, and Mr. Sanders.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Select Committee on
			 Ethics:</header><text>Mrs. Boxer (Chairman), Mr. Pryor, and Mr. Brown
			 (Ohio).</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph><committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Indian
			 Affairs:</header><text>Mr. Akaka (Chairman), Mr. Inouye, Mr. Conrad, Mr.
			 Johnson (South Dakota), Ms. Cantwell, Mr. Tester, Mr. Udall (New Mexico), and
			 Mr. Franken.</text>
			</committee-appointment-paragraph></section></resolution-body>
</resolution>
