<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="billres.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE resolution PUBLIC "-//US Congress//DTDs/res.dtd//EN" "res.dtd">
<resolution public-private="public" resolution-stage="Agreed-to-Senate" resolution-type="senate-resolution" star-print="no-star-print" key="G">
<metadata xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<dublinCore>
<dc:title>118 SRES 411 ATS: To constitute the majority party's membership on certain committees for the One Hundred Eighteenth Congress, or until their successors are chosen.</dc:title>
<dc:publisher>U.S. Senate</dc:publisher>
<dc:date>2023-10-17</dc:date>
<dc:format>text/xml</dc:format>
<dc:language>EN</dc:language>
<dc:rights>Pursuant to Title 17 Section 105 of the United States Code, this file is not subject to copyright protection and is in the public domain.</dc:rights>
</dublinCore>
</metadata>
<form>
<distribution-code display="yes">III</distribution-code>
<congress display="yes">118th CONGRESS</congress>
<session display="yes">1st Session</session>
<legis-num>S. RES. 411</legis-num>
<current-chamber>IN THE SENATE OF THE UNITED STATES</current-chamber>
<action display="yes">
<action-date date="20231017">October 17, 2023</action-date>
<action-desc><sponsor name-id="S270">Mr. Schumer</sponsor> submitted the following resolution; which was considered and agreed to</action-desc>
</action>
<legis-type>RESOLUTION</legis-type>
<official-title display="yes">To constitute the majority party's membership on certain committees for the One Hundred Eighteenth Congress, or until their successors are chosen.</official-title>
</form>
<resolution-body display-resolving-clause="yes-display-resolving-clause" style="OLC" id="H9F366DFB7A6049CDBC910D3681F491DB">
<section commented="no" display-inline="yes-display-inline" id="S1" section-type="undesignated-section"><text display-inline="yes-display-inline">the following shall constitute the majority party's membership on the following committees for the One Hundred Eighteenth Congress, or until their successors are chosen:</text> <committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Appropriations:</header><text>Mrs. Murray (Chair), Mr. Durbin, Mr. Reed, Mr. Tester, Mrs. Shaheen, Mr. Merkley, Mr. Coons, Mr. Schatz, Ms. Baldwin, Mr. Murphy, Mr. Manchin, Mr. Van Hollen, Mr. Heinrich, Mr. Peters, Ms. Sinema</text></committee-appointment-paragraph>

<committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs:</header><text>Mr. Brown (Chair), Mr. Reed, Mr. Menendez, Mr. Tester, Mr. Warner, Ms. Warren, Mr. Van Hollen, Ms. Cortez Masto, Ms. Smith, Mr. Warnock, Mr. Fetterman, Ms. Butler.</text></committee-appointment-paragraph> <committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Energy and Natural Resources:</header><text>Mr. Manchin (Chair), Mr. Wyden, Ms. Cantwell, Mr. Sanders, Mr. Heinrich, Ms. Hirono, Mr. King, Ms. Cortez Masto, Mr. Hickenlooper, Mr. Padilla.</text></committee-appointment-paragraph>

<committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Homeland Security and Governmental Affairs:</header><text>Mr. Peters (Chair), Mr. Carper, Ms. Hassan, Ms. Sinema, Ms. Rosen, Mr. Ossoff, Mr. Blumenthal, Ms. Butler.</text></committee-appointment-paragraph> <committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Select Committee on Intelligence:</header><text>Mr. Warner (Chair), Mr. Wyden, Mr. Heinrich, Mr. King, Mr. Bennet, Mr. Casey, Mrs. Gillibrand, Mr. Ossoff, Mr. Kelly, Mr. Reed (ex officio), Mr. Schumer (ex officio).</text></committee-appointment-paragraph>

<committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on the Judiciary:</header><text>Mr. Durbin (Chair), Mr. Whitehouse, Ms. Klobuchar, Mr. Coons, Mr. Blumenthal, Ms. Hirono, Mr. Booker, Mr. Padilla, Mr. Ossoff, Mr. Welch, Ms. Butler.</text></committee-appointment-paragraph> <committee-appointment-paragraph><header>Committee on Rules and Administration:</header><text>Ms. Klobuchar (Chair), Mr. Schumer, Mr. Warner, Mr. Merkley, Mr. Padilla, Mr. Ossoff, Mr. Bennet, Mr. Welch, Ms. Butler.</text></committee-appointment-paragraph>

</section>
</resolution-body>
</resolution> 


