<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="billres.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE resolution PUBLIC "-//US Congress//DTDs/res.dtd//EN" "res.dtd">
<resolution dms-id="H89778DC084D74F9CABF4DE10C820DA01" public-private="public" resolution-stage="Engrossed-in-House" resolution-type="house-resolution" star-print="no-star-print" key="H"> 
<form> 
<distribution-code display="no">IV</distribution-code> 
<congress display="no">111th CONGRESS</congress> 
<session display="no">1st Session</session> 
<legis-num>H. RES. 24</legis-num> 
<current-chamber display="yes">In the House of Representatives, U. S.,</current-chamber>
<action>
<action-date date="20090107">January 7, 2009</action-date>
</action> 
<legis-type display="yes">RESOLUTION</legis-type> 
<official-title display="no">Electing Members to certain standing committees of the House of Representatives.</official-title> 
</form> 
<resolution-body style="traditional" id="HC631F97CA4C0476884D84864BBB82100"> 
<section display-inline="yes-display-inline" section-type="undesignated-section" id="H33BB8488FCD745789C9C1FFC8D00C082"><text>That the following named Members be and are hereby elected to the following standing committees of the House of Representatives:</text>
<paragraph id="H355B06B31A474BF5BFEA5D6603D4DB6F" display-inline="no-display-inline"><enum>(1)</enum><header>Committee on Appropriations</header><text display-inline="yes-display-inline">Mr. Murtha, Mr. Dicks, Mr. Mollohan, Ms. Kaptur, Mr. Visclosky, Mrs. Lowey, Mr. Serrano, Ms. DeLauro, Mr. Moran of Virginia, Mr. Olver, Mr. Pastor, Mr. Price of North Carolina, Mr. Edwards, Mr. Kennedy of Rhode Island, Mr. Hinchey, Ms. Roybal-Allard, Mr. Farr, Mr. Jackson of Illinois, Ms. Kilpatrick of Michigan, Mr. Boyd of Florida, Mr. Fattah, Mr. Rothman, Mr. Bishop of Georgia, Mr. Berry, Ms. Lee, Mr. Schiff, Mr. Honda, Ms. McCollum of Minnesota, Mr. Israel, Mr. Ryan of Ohio, Mr. Ruppersberger, Mr. Chandler, Ms. Wasserman Schultz, Mr. Rodriguez, Mr. Lincoln Davis of Tennessee, Mr. Salazar.</text></paragraph>
<paragraph id="H84A39E6BFE6543B181D350CEED704FF1" display-inline="no-display-inline"><enum>(2)</enum><header>Committee on Armed Services</header><text display-inline="yes-display-inline">Mr. Spratt, Mr. Ortiz, Mr. Taylor, Mr. Abercrombie, Mr. Reyes, Mr. Snyder, Mr. Smith of Washington, Ms. Loretta Sanchez of California, Mr. McIntyre, Mrs. Tauscher, Mr. Brady of Pennsylvania, Mr. Andrews, Mrs. Davis of California, Mr. Langevin, Mr. Larsen of Washington, Mr. Cooper, Mr. Marshall, Ms. Bordallo, Mr. Boren, Mr. Ellsworth, Mr. Patrick Murphy of Pennsylvania, Mr. Johnson of Georgia, Ms. Shea-Porter, Mr. Courtney, Mr. Loebsack, Mrs. Gillibrand, Mr. Sestak, Ms. Giffords, Ms. Tsongas, Mr. Nye, Ms. Pingree of Maine, Mr. Kissell, Mr. Heinrich, Mr. Kravotil, Mr. Massa, Mr. Bright. </text></paragraph>
<paragraph id="HC577695F191E49F6B225033621D26B16" display-inline="no-display-inline"><enum>(3)</enum><header>Committee on Energy and Commerce</header><text display-inline="yes-display-inline">Mr. Dingell, Mr. Markey, Mr. Boucher, Mr. Pallone, Mr. Gordon of Tennessee, Mr. Rush, Ms. Eshoo, Mr. Stupak, Mr. Engel, Mr. Gene Green of Texas, Ms. DeGette, Mrs. Capps, Mr. Doyle, Ms. Harman, Ms. Schakowsky, Mr. Gonzalez, Mr. Inslee, Ms. Baldwin, Mr. Ross, Mr. Weiner, Mr. Matheson, Mr. Butterfield, Mr. Melancon, Mr. Barrow, Mr. Hill, Ms. Matsui, Mrs. Christensen, Ms. Castor, Mr. Sarbanes, Mr. Murphy of Connecticut, Mr. Space, Mr. McNerney, Ms. Sutton, Mr. Braley of Iowa, Mr. Welch.</text></paragraph>
<paragraph id="HB75325054F0A4CA6B8059DF8A9C8EAD2" display-inline="no-display-inline"><enum>(4)</enum><header>Committee on Financial Services</header><text display-inline="yes-display-inline">Mr. Kanjorski, Ms. Waters, Mrs. Maloney, Mr. Gutierrez, Ms. Velazquez, Mr. Watt, Mr. Ackerman, Mr. Sherman, Mr. Meeks of New York, Mr. Moore of Kansas, Mr. Capuano, Mr. Hinojosa, Mr. Clay, Mrs. McCarthy of New York, Mr. Baca, Mr. Lynch, Mr. Miller of North Carolina, Mr. Scott of Georgia, Mr. Al Green of Texas, Mr. Cleaver, Ms. Bean, Mr. Moore of Kansas, Mr. Hodes, Mr. Ellison, Mr. Klein of Florida, Mr. Wilson of Ohio, Mr. Perlmutter, Mr. Donnelly of Indiana, Mr. Foster, Mr. Carson of Indiana, Ms. Speier, Mr. Childers, Mr. Minnick, Mr. Adler of New Jersey, Ms. Kilroy, Mr. Driehaus, Ms. Kosmas, Mr. Grayson, Mr. Himes, Mr. Peters, Mr. Maffei.</text></paragraph>
<paragraph id="H36F8F8FCD4FE41D1B6B190B9BC76D873" display-inline="no-display-inline"><enum>(5)</enum><header>Committee on Transportation and Infrastructure</header><text display-inline="yes-display-inline">Mr. Rahall, Mr. DeFazio, Mr. Costello, Ms. Norton, Mr. Nadler of New York, Ms. Corrine Brown of Florida, Mr. Filner, Ms. Eddie Bernice Johnson of Texas, Mr. Taylor, Mr. Cummings, Mrs. Tauscher, Mr. Boswell, Mr. Holden, Mr. Baird, Mr. Larsen of Washington, Mr. Capuano, Mr. Bishop of Utah, Mr. Michaud, Mr. Carnahan, Mrs. Napolitano, Mr. Lipinski, Ms. Hirono, Mr. Altmire, Mr. Walz, Mr. Shuler, Mr. Arcuri, Mr. Mitchell, Mr. Carney, Mr. Hall of New York, Mr. Kagen, Mr. Cohen, Ms. Richardson, Mr. Sires, Ms. Edwards of Maryland, Mr. Ortiz, Mr. Hare, Mr. Boccieri, Mr. Schauer, Ms. Markey of Colorado, Mr. Griffith, Mr. McMahon, Mr. Perriello, Ms. Titus, Mr. Teague.</text></paragraph>
<paragraph id="HC97C8525098C4096B6E4C260F21D1056" display-inline="no-display-inline"><enum>(6)</enum><header>Committee on Ways and Means</header><text display-inline="yes-display-inline">Mr. Stark, Mr. Levin, Mr. McDermott, Mr. Lewis of Georgia, Mr. Neal of Massachusetts, Mr. Tanner, Mr. Becerra, Mr. Doggett, Mr. Pomeroy, Mr. Thompson of California, Mr. Larson of Connecticut, Mr. Blumenauer, Mr. Kind, Mr. Pascrell, Ms. Berkley, Mr. Crowley, Mr. Van Hollen, Mr. Meek of Florida, Ms. Schwartz of Pennsylvania, Mr. Davis of Alabama, Mr. Davis of Illinois, Mr. Etheridge, Ms. Linda T. Sanchez of California, Mr. Higgins, Mr. Yarmuth.</text></paragraph></section> 
</resolution-body> 
<attestation><attestation-group><attestor display="no">Lorraine C. Miller,</attestor><role>Clerk.</role></attestation-group></attestation>
</resolution> 
